충분치 않아.
더 필요 해.
Not big enough--
we need more.
더 있지.
We got more.
당분간 내가 가면
안될 곳이라도 있나?
Any, uh, places I should avoid
in the next few days?
로스 엔젤레스.
Los Angeles.
그렇군.
Right.
거래하게 돼서
즐거웠네, 친구들.
Pleasure doing business
with you, amigos.
거래 완료.
Sale complete.
FBI다!
FBI!
엔진 꺼!
Turn off your engine!
FBI다!
FBI!
손 든채
차에서 내려!
Exit the vehicle
with your hands up!
천천히.
Slowly.
너, 저놈들 체포 해.
You, get 'em up.
손은
머리에.
Hands on your head.
돌아 서.
Turn around.
좋아, 수갑 채워.
All right, cuff him.
Right here...
완료.
Clear.
잘 했네,
나즈리 요원.
Good work, Agent Nasri.
정말
안타깝네요.
Real shame.
이제 막
즐기기 시작했는데.
I was starting
to enjoy their company.
정말로?
Really?
Yeah.
그간 도청을
계속 들었는데
Man, I've been listening
to their wiretaps,
그놈들은
네게 질색을 하던데.
and they were getting
really sick of you.
C-4 폭탄
챙겨.
Secure the C-4.
국장한텐
내가 알릴게.
I'll notify
the director.
앞을
조사해 봐.
Check the front.
당신은
날 따라 와.
All right.
You're with me.
컨웨이
요원입니다.
Agent Conway.
국장님 좀
부탁합니다.
The director, please.
예 써.
Yes, sir.
작전은
성공했습니다.
The op was a success.
넵. 법무장관 사무실엔
제가 알리겠습니다.
Yes, sir, I'll notify
the A.G.'s office.
오늘 안으로 필요한건
그들이 전부
가지고 있을겁니다.
They should have everything
they need by the end of the day.
♪ NCIS: LA 6x18 ♪
Fighting Shadows
방송일: 2015년 3월23일
??NCIS: LA 6x18 ??/font>
Fighting Shadows
Original Air Date on March 23, 2015
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
한글자막 및 싱크 재조정: 비키남.
?? ??
마지막이야.
- Okay, last one.
- Come on, last one.
자 해보자.
땅을 박차!
Let's do this, attack the ground!
땅을 박차라고!
Attack the ground!
왜 우린 보통 사람처럼
뛰면 안되는거지?
I don't know why we can't run
like normal human beings.
이거 되게 이상하고
부자연 스러운데.
This is so weird and unnatural.
샐리 놀이는
그만 해.
Quit being a Sally.
이제 넌 있는 줄도 몰랐던
근육이 생길꺼야.
You'll find muscles
you never knew you had.
무슨 소리 하는거야?
What are you
talking about?
있어야 할 근육은
전부 다 있다구.
I've got muscles
in all the right places.
난 마르고 기름기없는
섹스머신이야.
I'm a lean, mean
sex machine.
내 애인이
그러더라구.
Or that's what
my, uh, ladybird says.
난 그런 말
한 일 없는데.
I never said that.
3일전에 분명
나한테 그랬다고.
Yeah, you said it
to me three days ago.
사실은 넌
내 귀에...
You actually
whispered it...
속삭였어.
in my ear.
내 귀를
물었잖아.
You bit said ear.
좀 아프긴 했지만
사실 꽤 좋았어.
Which kind of hurt,
but I also kind of liked it.
그래? 그럼
그거 취소할게.
Huh, yeah, well,
I take it back.
취소가 안돼지.
You can't
take it back.
아직 내 귀에
이빨 자국이 있다구.
I still have little
teeth marks on my ear.
아니, 내가 너보고
섹스머신이라고
Yeah, no, I mean
I take back saying
한 말을
취소 한다고.
that you're a
sex machine.
Oh, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
오, 그래?
그럼 지금 여기서
당장 증명해 보여줘?
Want me to prove it to you
right here and right now?
알았어. 쳐다보진 마
Okay, don't look now,
네 5시 방향에
카메라든 여자가 있어.
but your five o'clock,
woman with a camera.
내가 방금 뭐라 그랬지?
쳐다보지 말랬잖아.
What did I just say?
I said don't look.
뭐, 그건
자연스러운 거 였다구.
What?
That was natural.
번호판이 없네.
No plates.
그 여자가 우리 사진
찍고 있던게 확실 해?
Sure she was
taking photos of us?
그래, 내말은...
Yeah, I mean...
잘 몰라, 내가 너무
신경과민인가?
I don't know, you think
I'm being paranoid?
작전에 우리가
필요했던게지.
I think they need
us in Ops.
살았다!
Look alive!
FBI!
모하비 사막,
1시간 전이야.
Mojave Desert, one hour ago.
FBI는 자생적 테러리스트
토벌 작전인 '벌침' 작전의
The FBI was in the final
stage of a sting operation
마지막 단계에
있었습니다.
with some homegrown
terrorists.
C4 거래가 완료되고
놈들을 체포한 직 후
They had just completed a sale
of C-4 and arrested the men
이 일이 벌어졌죠.
when this happened.
몇이나 죽었지?
How many dead?
요원 3명 입니다.
Three agents
그 중엔 잘릴 나즈리
라는 요원도 있었는데
including Agent
Jalil Nasri,
그는 지난 4개월 동안
who had been undercover
with the suspects
그 용의자들 틈에
잠복 근무중이었습니다.
for the last four months.
그는 신뢰를 얻은 후,
He gained their trust,
군 측 딜러를 놈들에게
소개했습니다.
introduced them
to an arms dealer...
그도 역시 FBI 요원
이었던 사람입니다.
Who also happened
to be an FBI agent.
거래가 끝나자
테러리스트도 끝났죠.
Sale went down,
so did the terrorists.
9/11 테러 이후
이런 벌침작전은
Since 9/11,
these sting operations
일상화
되었습니다.
have become common practice.
그래, 그럼 뭐가
잘못 된던거지?
Okay, so what
went wrong?
그 두 테러리스트가
뇌관을 설치했나?
Did the two terrorists
set a detonator?
그런것 같진 않습니다.
그들은 C4에 손도 안댔거든요.
Well, it's unlikely, because
they never touched the C-4.
그건 우리측 잠복 요원으로부터
또다른 요원에게 건네졌어요.
It was passed from one
undercover agent to the next.
FBI가 전체 작전동안
꼭 쥐고 있었죠.
The FBI had it
in their custody the entire op.
그래 FBI가 우리보고
이번 사건 수사를
도와 달라는건가?
So the FBI wants our help
with this investigation?
명령에 가깝죠.
More like our heads.
C4는 국방성으로부터
빌린겁니다.
C-4 was on loan from the DoD.
철저히 관리 되야하는
방어용 군수품입니다.
It's considered controlled
defense material.
그렇담 이건 책임소재에
관한 문젠건가?
Wait, so this is
about liability?
해군청은 폭발물
납품 업체와 관련된
SECNAV wants assurance
that there was no problem
문제가 아니라는
확신을 원합니다.
with the supply
of explosives.
만일 문제가
있다면...
If so...
다른 작전들도
위험하다는 얘기지.
Other operations
could be at risk.
그리고 국방성은
민사소송을 당할거구요.
And it opens up the DoD
to a civil lawsuit.
왜, 캘리포니아 변호사역을
다시하고 싶은가, 딕스군?
You thinking of retaking
the California Bar, Mr. Deeks?
3일간의
지옥이요?
Three days of hell?
차라리 켄지 아파트를
반 정도 치우겠습니다.
I'd rather clean half
of Kensi's apartment.
잘 기억해 둘게.
I keep offering.
그럼 그때까지
자네와 캘런은
Well, until that time,
I'd like you and Mr. Callen
해군 C4 공급선에
문제가 없는지
확인해 보도록.
to ensure that the Navy's C-4
supply hasn't been compromised.
저와 캘런이라고
하셨습니까?
You-- it sounded like
you said me and Callen.
딕스와
저라구요?
Deeks and me?
미스터 해나,
Mr. Hanna,
자네와
블라이양은
I'd like you
and Ms. Blye
사건 현장에
나가보게.
to handle the
crime scene.
네, 혹시 뭐...?
Uh, is there any...?
음... 됐슴돠.
Hmm... okay.
내 생각에
우리...
I guess we're...
Okay.
NCIS 입니다.
윈터스 중위를
잧고 있습니다.
NCIS, looking for First
Lieutenant Winters.
잠시만요.
One moment.
중위님,
NCIS가 와있습니다.
Lieutenant, NCIS is here.
그럼, 에 또...
So, uh...
예 써.
Yes, sir.
조엘은 잘있나?
...Joelle's good?
잘 있지.
She's good.
아주 잘.
She's great.
잘 됐군.
Great.
잘, 잘, 잘.
Great, great, great.
켄지는 어떤가?
How's Kensi?
에... 켄지...
그녀는...
Uh, Kensi's...
she's...
잘 있잖아요.
you know, she's good.
그걸 왜 나한테
물어보는거죠?
I don't know
why you're asking me.
선배도 그녀와
같이 일 하잖아.
I mean, you work with her,
you know she's...
선배도 그녀가
잘 있는거 알 잖아.
she's good, right?
Mm-hmm.
그러게, 내가 왜
물어 봤을까...
Because I don't know
why I would have any...
뭔데요?
What?
선배, 알고있구나.
그렇죠?
You know, don't you?
물론 알지.
Of course I know.
누가 또 아나요?
Who else knows?
어디보자...
Well, let's see.
샘, 넬,
헤티는 물론이고
Sam, Nell,
Hetty, of course.
에릭은 시간이 좀
걸렸지만 결국 알게됐고.
Eric took a little while,
but he finally got there.
차량 관리과
직원들.
The guys in
the motor pool.
거의 대부분이
알고있지.
Pretty much everyone
at this point.
그랜저는?
What about Granger?
그랜저는
잘 모르겠는데.
Granger I'm not
so sure about.
그는 지난 중독사건
이후로 확실히
Uh, he's definitely mellowed
since the poisoning,
부드러워지긴 했는데,
언젠가 너희 두명을 혼내려
but he... he could just
be biding his time,
벼르고 있는지도 몰라.
waiting for the right
moment to crush you both.
그거참...
무섭구만.
Well, that is...
awesome.
Mm-hmm.
그럴줄 몰랐다는
척 하지마.
Don't pretend like you
didn't know the risks.
이 파트너 교체가
아무래도 우리 일과
I'm just wondering
if this partner shuffle
관련이 있지 않나
생각이 드네요.
has something
to do with us.
그 답은 오직 헤티만
할 수 있지.
That is a question
only Hetty can answer.
전 캘런 요원이고,
이쪽은 딕스 형삽니다.
Agent Callen,
Detective Deeks.
안녕하십니까?
How are you?
네, 이리로
들어 오시죠.
All right,
come on in.
이게 FBI로부터 받은 것과
동일한 C4입니다.
This is the same lot of C-4
we drew from for the FBI.
제가 직접 모든
일급 폭발물들의
I personally oversee
the transfer
이동을 감독합니다.
of all Class-A
explosives,
교본에 나온 그대로
따랐습니다.
I can tell you-- protocol was
followed to the letter.
테스트는
해 봤습니까?
Has it been tested?
여러분들이
여기 오기 전에
Just before you arrived,
표준 화염 및 충격
테스트를 해 봤습니다.
I conducted standard burn
and impact tests.
예상된 성능을
보였습니다.
Performed as expected.
어떘는데요?
And how is that?
터져야 할때 터지고
안터져야 할때 안터졌습니다.
Blew up when it was supposed to,
didn't when it wasn't.
FBI 작전 중에 이
C4를 터트리려면.
For this C-4 to detonate
during the FBI's op,
뇌관이
필요했을겁니다.
it would've needed a primer.
하지만 우린 그걸
주지 않았습니다.
And we didn't
supply them with one.
다른 누군가가
줬단 얘기네.
Which means somebody else did.
실례합니다,
제가...
Excuse me, can I...?
잠시 좀 봐도
될까요?
Can I please have a minute?
뭔가 신경
쓰이는 게 있나봐요?
Something's
bothering you.
왜 그렇게 보이나?
Why do you say that?
얼굴 표정이 꼭
딕스가 피스타치오
The look
on your face is the same
먹을때랑
똑 같아서.
as when Deeks eats pistachios.
걘 껍질을 사방에 흘려.
지저분 하게 시리.
He gets the shells everywhere--
it's disgusting.
내가 일러 둘께요.
무슨 일이죠?
All right, I'll have
a talk with him. What's up?
충분히 크질 않아.
It's not big enough.
무슨 얘기죠?
What do you mean?
C4 10파운드면
Ten pounds of C-4,
파편이 반 마일은
퍼졌을 텐데.
the debris should be
half a mile away.
그럼 전부가 터진게
아니라고 생각하나요?
So, are you thinking
not all of it exploded?
아니, 이럴 수가.
You got to be
kidding me.
뭔가요?
What do you got?
밴에 하나 가득있던,
C4라고 생각 했던거.
A van full of C-4 explodes,
you assume it was the C-4.
가방이 돌들로
채워져 있어.
Case was lined
with pumice.
충격을
흡수하지.
Absorbs the shock.
그럼 밴 안에 다른
폭탄이 있었군요.
So there was another bomb
on the van.
원격으로 폭파
시켰을 꺼야.
I'm thinking remote detonation.
결정적인 순간을
노렸겠지.
They waited
for the precise moment
FBI 요원 혼자
폭발 범위에 있는
순간을.
when only the FBI agents were
in the blast zone.
저기에요.
There.
나라면 저기
있겠어요.
That's where I'd be.
벌침과 체포 작전이
한눈에 들어오는 곳이군.
Perfect vantage point
for the sting and take down.
남쪽으로의 도주로
접근도 용이하군.
Good access to the roads
leading south.
여기 발자국을
찾았어요.
We got footprints.
사이즈는
11 같고,
Looks like a size 11.
작업화고
Work boots.
남자것 같아
보이네요.
Most likely male.
여기 타이어 자국도
찾았어요.
I got tire
tracks, too.
이걸 에릭에게
보내야 겠군.
I'll send these
over to Eric.
켄지.
Kensi.
피스타치오 표정이네요,
무슨 일이죠?
You got pistachio face--
what's up?
비밀 벌침 작전에서
세명의 FBI요원을
정확히 골라내 죽이다니
Taking out three FBI agents
in a secret sting operation,
아주 놀랍구만.
that's impressive.
이런 킬러는 보통
단서를 이렇게 많이
흘리지 않는데.
A killer like this doesn't
usually leave this many clues.
메시지를 보내려는게
아니라면 말이지.
Unless he's sending a message.
현장에 남있던
타이어 자국을 보니
Based on the tire tracks
left at the crime scene,
구 모델 승합차
같습니다.
we're probably looking
for an older-model SUV.
2000년대 초반.
Early 2000s.
'만화경'엔 뭐
딴거 없어?
Anything from
Kaleidoscope?
우린 이걸로
일해야 합니다.
This is what
we have to work with--
20 평방마일 안에
아무것도 없습니다.
20 square miles
of nothing,
감시 카메라도
없습니다.
and that
includes cameras.
FBI 자원이 피습으로 인해
부족해진 관계로
Now the FBI's resources
are strained, so...
그들은 샘과 켄지에게
그 차량을 지상 추적토록
하고 있습니다.
they're letting Sam and Kensi
track the vehicle on the ground.
그 타이어 자국이
카메라가 있는
Our hope is that the
tire tracks lead
도로로 이어지길
기대하고 있습니다.
to a road with a camera.
그들이 찾은
시계는?
What about
the watch they found?
3000개가 넘는
온라인 상점에서
팔리는 겁니다.
Sold in over
3,000 stores online.
1년에 최소 800개는
팔립니다.
At least 800
sold every year.
추적이 불가능하죠.
Impossible to trace.
바늘이 5:37에
멈췄어.
Hands are stopped at 5:37.
똑딱소리 안 나는
똑딱시계
Ticking clock
without the ticking.
- 지문 채취는했나?
- 지금 하는 중입니다.
- Has it been dusted for prints?
- That's happening now.
결과가 나오면
알려 드리겠습니다.
I'll let you know
when the report comes in.
다른 어떤 놈이
그 밴에다 폭탄을 뒸어.
Someone else placed
a bomb on this van.
어떻게 된 일인지
밴 주인이 알지도 몰라.
Maybe the van's owners have
an idea how this happened.
데미어 말키는
Well, Demir Malki was hit
파편에 맞았습니다.
with shrapnel
from the blast.
그는 지금 수술 중이고
그의 형 도간이
He's in surgery.
And his brother Dogan
FBI에 잡혀
있습니다.
is in custody
at the FBI's
마르 비스타에 있는
비밀작전 특별팀
사무실에.
Undercover Task Force
offices in Mar Vista.
가서 도간과
얘길 해 봅시다.
Let's go talk to Dogan.
바로 쫓아 갈게요.
잠시 들릴 곳이 있어요.
I'll catch up with you.
I got one stop to make.
얼마나 뒤로
돌릴까요?
How far back should I go?
맨 뒤로.
All the way back.
헤티, 저기요, 우린...
Hetty, hey, listen,
we need to...
와, 저건...?
Whoa! What are...?
누구였죠?
Who was that?
누구 말이야?
Uh, who was who?
방금 화면에
나왔던 여자.
그게 누구죠?
The woman on the screen that
was just up there-- who is that?
그 여자가 오늘 아침
저와 켄지 사진을
찍고 있었어요.
That woman was taking pictures
of me and Kensi this morning.
이런, 젠장.
Oh, damn.
헤티, 무슨 일이죠?
Hetty, what's going on?
내가 지금 조사 중
이라는 말 밖엔
All I can tell you, Mr. Deeks,
해 줄 수 없네,
딕스군.
is that I'm looking into it.
네...
저기, 음...
Right. Listen, uh...
헤티, 만일 그녀가
위협적이라면
Hetty, if she's
some sort of threat,
제 생각에
우린...
I think that we should...
아니, 위협적인
존재가 아니라네.
No, she is not a threat.
- 아직은 말이지.
- 아직 이군요.
Not yet.
중요한건,
What is imperative
자네와
is that you
블라이 양은 오늘
반드시 떨어져 있어야
and Ms. Blye stay apart
한다는거야.
for today.
내 말 이해가 됐나?
Am I understood?
헤티, 그건, 음...
Hetty, it's, um...
딕스군,
예스야 노야?
Mr. Deeks, yes or no.
예스입니다.
Yes.
비공식적으로는
노 입니다.
With an
off-the-record no.
알았네.
좋아.
All right. Good.
Okay.
일부러 그에게
사진을 보여줬죠,
안그랬나요?
You let him see the photo
on purpose, didn't you?
그가 얼마나
알고 있는지
알고 싶었네.
I wanted to know
how much he knew.
이젠 알게 됐다네.
Now I know.
존스양,
하던일 계속하게.
Back to work, Ms. Jones.
왜 우리에게
얘기 안해줬어?
Why didn't you tell us?
우린 너희들
프라이버시를
존중했지.
We were respecting
your privacy.
우릴 괜찮다고
보시나요?
And you're okay with this?
사내 연애가
괜찮냐면? 노.
Am I okay with my
coworkers dating? No.
네가 팀에서 빠지길
바란다는 얘기냐면?
절대, 노.
Does that mean I want you
off the team? Hell, no.
딕스에게도
마찬가지지.
And that goes
for Deeks, too.
걔한텐 내가
이말 했다고 하지마.
Oh, well...
Don't tell him I said that.
안 할게요.
I will not.
너희들은 결국
그일이 어디로
It's just, you know,
eventually, you guys
흘러 갈건지
알게 될거야.
are gonna have to figure out
where this thing is going.
계속해서 네 목숨을
조준선 상에 내놓고
싶진 않을거아냐.
You don't want to continue to
put your lives on the line.
무슨 말이지?
Meaning what?
뭔 말이냐면,
Meaning that...
미쉘과 내가 캠을
가졌을때
when Michelle and I had Kam,
그건 완전 또 다른
임무 더구만.
that was a whole nother mission.
애들.
Kids.
그래, 아니.
Yeah, no.
노 노 노 노 노
No, no, no, no, no.
우린, 우리는
We're not, we're not...
애들 생각은
없는데.
we're not thinking about kids.
우린 저녁 같이 먹을
생각조차 없어요.
We're not even thinking
about dinner.
그건 좋아.
하지만 일이라는게 늘
계획대로만 되진 않지.
That's fine, but things don't
always go as they're planned.
일이 생기고,
애도 생기고.
Things happen.
Kids happen.
그게 바로 에이든 한테
일어난 일이야.
That's what happened
with Aiden, he kind of...
말하자면 걘,
어느날 갑자기 생겼지.
popped up out of the blue.
난 내가 모든일에
준비가 돼 있다고
생각했는데,
I thought I was ready
for anything--
active duty, whatever--
but not for that.
군복무든 뭐든.
하지만 그일엔
아니었지.
난 완벽한 아빠도
아니었어.
I wasn't a perfect
dad, either.
처음 일년 동안은
엄청난 시행착오를
했었지.
I made a lot of mistakes
those first years.
난 에이든이 행운아
인거 같은데.
I think Aiden was a lucky kid.
내가 행운아 였어.
I was the lucky one.
지금도 그렇지만.
Still am.
우리의 테러범
도간 말키는
So our terrorist, Dogan Malki,
아직 아무말고
않고 있습니다.
hasn't said a word to us.
보통 전 그런걸
용납하지 않는데
Normally I wouldn't
allow this,
but since the attack...
지난번 공격 이후
일손이 좀
부족하네요.
we've been
a little shorthanded.
시작해 보세요.
Have at him.
도간 말키.
Dogan Malki.
와우, 피가
많이 묻었군.
Wow, that is quite
the... bloodstain.
동생한테서
묻은건가 보지?
That's from your
younger brother, right?
FBI가 그러는데,
말하기 싫다며?
FBI says
you don't like to talk.
어쨌든 좋아.
듣기만 해도 돼.
That's fine.
Just listen.
네 동생 데미어가
죽어가고 있어.
Your brother Demir
is dying.
파편이 그의 신장을
찟어 발겼네.
The shrapnel ripped
apart his kidneys.
당장 이식을
받아야 해.
He needs a new one
immediately.
너도 알겠지만,
테러범이라고 해서
As you can probably imagine,
being a terrorist
이식 대기자 명단
제일 위로 올려 주진 않아.
doesn't put you very high on the
priority list for transplants.
하지만
다행인 것은
The good news--
for you, of course--
가족들이 기증 하겠다면
예외로 해 주지.
being that they make
exceptions for family.
예, 예.
물론입니다.
Y-Yes... yes, of course.
제 신장을
주겠습니다.
I'll give him mine.
가슴이
훈훈해 지는군.
Well, that is actively
heartwarming.
한가지 작은
There's just one
문제가 있네.
small problem.
FBI는 자네와
자네 동생이
The FBI thinks
you and your brother
요원 3명을
죽였다고 생각해.
killed three of their agents.
그들이 널
안 보내 줄거야.
They're not letting you
go anywhere.
하지만, 어.. 우린
그들을 죽이지
않았습니다.
But, uh... we didn't kill them.
흠. 그렇다면 어떻게
폭탄이 밴에 있었을까?
Hmm. So how did the bomb
get in the van?
제가 그걸
어떻게 압니까?
How would I know?
제발요... 제 동생은
제 도움이 필요합니다.
Please... my-my brother
needs my help.
생각을 해,
도간.
Think, Dogan!
밴을 누구한테
빌려준 일 있나?
Did you loan the van to anyone?
최근 밴으로
어딜 갔었나?
Did you take it
anywhere recently?
모 모 몰라요..
I-I-I-I, I don't...
세차장,
발렛 파킹.
A car wash, valet parking.
생각이 안나요!
I don't remember!
네 동생이
죽어가고 있어!
Your brother is dying!
정비소.
A mechanic.
제 제 제가 정비소에
가져갔었습니다.
I-I-I t-took it to a mechanic.
닷새 전에
펑크가 났었거든요.
We had a flat tire,
uh, about five days ago.
견인차가 약 1분 후에
나타났습니다.
A tow truck came by
about a minute later.
그들이 차를 밸리에 있는
정비소로 끌고 갔습니다.
They took it to a shop
in the Valley.
정비소 이름을
기억하나요?
What was the name of the shop?
레익뷰.
Lakeview.
레익뷰 차량 정비소
였습니다.
Lakeview Auto Repair.
저기요, 제 신장은
어떻게 되는거죠?
Wait, what about my kidney?
아, 참.
걍 넣어 두세요.
Oh, yeah,
you can keep your kidney,
동생은
괜찮으니까.
'cause your brother's fine.
모두 어디 간거죠?
So where is everyone?
켄지...
Kensi...
누군가 험한길을
다녀온 모양이군요.
Looks like
somebody's been off-roading.
연방 요원닷!
Federal agents!
무기를 내려 놔.
Drop your weapon.
내려 놧!
Drop it!
제가 모두 집에
돌려 보냈습니다.
I sent everyone
home for the day.
손 들어.
Hands up.
전 비무장입니다.
I'm unarmed.
절 그렇게 빨리
찾을 줄 몰랐군요.
I didn't think
you'd find me so quickly.
If you...
저기...
하지마.
Don't.
죄송.. 전 그냥
I'm sorry-- I was trying to say,
저기 서랍안에
if you check the top drawer,
찾으시는 게
있을거란 얘길 하려구...
you'll find
what you're looking for.
샘...
Sam...
원격 폭파장치.
Remote detonator.
당신들, FBI요원 3명을 죽인
폭탄을 설치한 사람을
You're searching for the person
who planted a bomb and killed
찾고있죠?
three FBI agents.
그를 찾으신겁니다.
You have found him.
체포에 저항하지 않겠다고
약속합니다.
I promise you,
I will not resist arrest.
또 한가지
약속할 건...
But I also promise...
오늘 아침의
공격이
this morning's attack
오늘의 유일한 공격이
아닐거라는 겁니다.
will not be the only one today.
그의 이름은
바킬 샤하입니다.
His name is Vakeel Shah.
20년전
파키스탄에서
이민왔습니다.
He immigrated here,
from Pakistan, 20 years ago.
아직까지 어떤
법적 문제도 야기한
일이 없습니다.
He's never been in
any trouble with the law.
세금도 잘 내고,
성공적인 정비소
사업도 시작했습니다.
He pays his taxes, started a
successful auto repair business.
그런데 무슨 일이
있었나요?
Okay, so what happened?
6년전 그의 형과 형수가
차 사고로 죽었습니다.
His brother and sister-in-law
died six years ago-- car crash.
샤하는 형의 아들
나비드를 데려갔습니다.
Shah took in their son Naveed.
우린 나비드를
체포했었습니다.
We arrested Naveed...
작년 벌침작전 때
말이죠.
in a sting operation
last year.
가짜 폭탄조끼를 입고
다니던 고등학교에
걸어 들어갔습니다.
He walked into his high school
wearing a dummy suicide vest.
당신이
준 거군요.
That you provided him.
제가 작전을 지휘했고
나즈리 요원은
잠복 중이 었습니다.
I ran the op and Agent Nasri
was undercover.
본론으로
돌아갑시다.
Let's stay on track here.
이 시계에 대해
알려 주세요.
Why don't you tell us
about this watch?
그건 나비드 것
입니다.
That's Naveed's.
그를 체포하다
망가졌습니다.
It was broken
during his arrest--
난폭하게 굴었거든요.
he got physical--
Shah must've claimed it
샤하가 재판이 끝나면
돌려달라고 할겁니다.
upon completion of the trial.
에릭이 시계에서
샤하의 지문이
나왔다고 했습니다.
Eric said the forensic team
pulled Shah's print off it.
우리가 그를
어떻게 찾았든 간에
Meaning, regardless
of how we found him,
이 시계가 우릴
샤하에게로
인도한 거군요.
this watch would've
lead us to Shah.
그가 자기를
찾아주길
바란겁니다.
He wanted to be found.
또한, 우리에게
두번째 공격에 대해
알려주고 싶었던거야.
And he wanted to tell us
about the second attack.
왜지?
Why?
심문할 때 확실히
물어봐 줄께요.
Well, I'll be sure to ask him
when I question him.
그렇게
안될겁니다.
Not happening.
뭐라구요?
Excuse me?
샤하는 그의 조카에게
일어난일에 대해
Shah clearly has a beef
with the FBI
분명 FBI에
불만이 있을텐데
for what went down
with his nephew,
당신이 바로 그 중심에
있기 때문이죠.
and you're at
the center of that.
외부인으로 하여금
심문토록 하는게
좋을겁니다.
It's better for an outside party
to do the questioning.
No.
만약 그가 무슨
말을 하게되면
If he says anything,
제일 먼저 알려
드리겠습니다.
you'll be the first to know.
그는 제 요원들을
죽였어요.
Right-- he killed my agents.
살살 다루시면
안됩니다.
Don't go easy on him.
So,
샤하의 조카 나비드는
빅터빌에 있습니다.
Shah's nephew, uh, Naveed,
is up at Victorville.
제가 그리로 가서 그가
곧 있을 그의 삼촌의
공격에 대해
I'm gonna go over there
and talk to him,
뭔가 알고 있는지
see if he knows anything
알아보겠습니다.
about, uh, his uncle's
impending attack.
좋아, 내가
같이 갈께요.
All right.
I'll go with you.
아.. 아니
내 생각에...
Yeah, no, I...
I think I'm gonna...
나 혼자 가야
할 것 같아.
I'm gonna probably go by myself.
내가 지난번
조사해 봤는데,
Okay, the last I checked,
내가 너보다 테러범들을
더 많이 심문 해 봤더구만.
그래서...
I had interrogated more
terrorists than you, so...
그건 그래...
Yeah.
심문이라고?
Interrogation?
당근이지.
Definitely.
어... 내가,
뭐라고 그랬나?
Oh... did I,
did I say something?
우리가 뭘
잘못한건가?
Did we do something wrong?
좀전에, 헤티가
걱정하는 걸
알게됐어.
I just know that
Hetty's worried.
내가 오늘 아침에
본 그 여자.
The woman I saw
this morning.
그게 누군데?
All right, who is she?
네가 헤티한테
답을 얻어내면
Well, if you can get
Hetty to answer that,
내가 네 아파트
청소해 줄께.
I actually will
clean your apartment.
노 노 노 노
하지마.
No, no, no,
don't do that.
헤티가 조사하는
중 이니까
Listen, Hetty's
looking into it,
걱정하게 놔 둬.
so let her be worried.
그래, 으음...
Okay, um...
알았어.
Fine.
난 가서 차 정비소를
조사해 볼께.
I'm gonna go
check out the auto shop
혹시 뭔가
나오나 봐야지.
and see what else
I can find.
잠간만,
헤이 헤이 헤이.
Hold on a second-- hey.
Hey, hey.
뭐?
What?
우리사인
괜찮아. 오케이?
You and I, we're good.
암껏두 우릴
갈라놓지 못해.
Okay? Nothing's gonna
tear us apart.
말해. 말해 보라구
"우린 괜찮아"라고.
Say it.
Say "We're good."
우린 괜찮아.
We're good.
좋아.
Okay.
저는 제 자백을
철회할
I have no intention
of retracting
용의가 없습니다,
해나 요원.
my confession, Agent Hanna.
어쩃든 제가 한건
제가 한겁니다.
What I did, I did.
진실을 밝히기 위해
그랬습니다.
But I did it so that
the truth would be revealed.
샤하씨, 우리가
관심있어 하는 건
오직
Mr. Shaw, the only truth
we're interested in
다음 공격이 언제
어디서 일어날 건가
하는겁니다.
is where and when this next
attack is going to take place.
그것 도 역시
밝혀질 겁니다.
That will also be revealed.
때가 되면
말이죠.
But only at the right time.
지금은 왜 그랬는지
이해하는게
좋을겁니다.
For now,
I'd rather you understand why.
왜라니, 뭐가?
Why what?
어째서 제가 제 주장을
알리기 위해
살인을 해야만 했는지.
Why I had to resort to killing
to make my point.
가볍게 내린 결정이
아니었습니다.
It is not a decision
I made lightly.
그렇담,
죽은 요원들의
가족들은
I'm sure the families
of those dead agents
그 안에서 평안을
찾게 되겠지.
will find comfort in that.
강조해 말
할 수 있습니다.
I can empathize.
그들의 고통을
느낍니다.
I feel their pain.
전 제 조카를
테러에 의해
잃었습니다.
I lost my nephew to terrorism.
당신 조카는
테러범이었어.
Your nephew was a terrorist.
엄청난 의견차군요.
That is a big distinction.
이 사건이 있기 전
그는 평범한 아이
였습니다.
But before this, he was a boy.
그게 바로 제가
말하려고 하는 것입니다.
This is what
I'm trying to tell you:
나비드는 테러범이
아니었습니다.
Naveed was not a terrorist
FBI가 그를 그렇게
만들기 전까지는 요.
until the FBI
turned him into one.
그는 착한
젊은이였죠.
He was a good young man.
그는 제 샵에서
일 했었습니다.
He worked at my shop--
수리공들을 돕고,
등록법을 배웠습니다.
helping the mechanics,
learning the register.
이 시계는...
제가 준겁니다.
This watch--
I gave him this watch
제시간에 출근해서
to motivate him
to show up on time,
빨리 일하고,
to work quickly,
책임감을 갖도록 하기
위해서 말입니다.
take responsibility.
그런데 어느날
BFI가 왔습니다.
But then the FBI came.
그들이 그를 그 길로
인도한겁니다.
They were the ones who
led him down that path...
온라인 비디오에서나 나오는
급진적 종교 지도자가 아니라
not some online videos
of radical imams.
바로 당신,
당신네 요원이
이끈겁니다.
It was you--
your federal agents.
그들이 그가
공격 못하도록
막았 잖습니까.
They stopped him from
carrying out an attack.
그 공격은 그들이
시킨겁니다.
An attack they provided him.
혼란스러워 하는
젊은이를 데려다가
You take confused young men,
도와주지는
못할 망정
and instead
of offering them help,
그들에게 테러 모의를
시킵니다.
you give them a plan.
그리고는 그들에게
폭탄을 팔죠.
And then you sell
them a bomb.
당신들의 적을,
테러를, 스스로
만드는 겁니다.
You create your own enemy,
your own terror.
So, who then
그렇다면, 누가
진짜 테러리스트
일까요?
is the real terrorist?
헤티의 슈퍼 비밀
프로젝트인가?
Super secret
Hetty project?
그리 비밀도 아냐.
Not so secret
분명히.
apparently.
그녀가 의도적으로
이 일들을 벌였다고
생각해 본적 없어?
Did you ever think she does
this sort of thing on purpose?
뭔가 비밀을
유지하고 있다가
Keep something secret
and then leak just
오직 필요한
사람에게만 살짝
the right amount
of information
필요한 정보를
흘리는 거야.
to just the right people.
그리곤 무슨일이
일어 나나
보는거지.
You know, to see what happens.
그래, 흔들어서
뭔가를 흘리는구만.
Yeah, shake things loose.
그래, 이건 마치...
체스 게임을
이기기 위해
Yeah, it's like...
일부러 체스 말을
it's like losing a chess piece
잡혀주는 것
같은거야.
in order to win the game.
난 체스 말
잡히는거
싫어 해.
You know I don't like
losing chess pieces.
알아.
I know.
넌 내가 네 쫄을
잡았을때 울었지.
You cried when
I took your pawn.
난 그게 무지
기분나빠, 알아?
I just feel so bad
for them, you know?
다음부턴
체커 게임이나 하자.
We'll stick to
checkers next time.
그래.
Okay.
이젠 가도 돼.
You can go now.
알았어.
Cool.
뭐야 저건 또.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
연방 요원이다!
Federal agent!
차에서 나와!
Get out of the car!
괜찮아요,
경찰입니다.
It's okay,
I'm a cop.
신분을
밝혀봐요.
Identify yourself.
재클린 리베라
형삽니다.
Detective Jacqueline Rivera.
LAPD 내사과
소속입니다.
LAPD Internal Affairs.
연방요원은
당신 권한
밖이요, 형사.
Federal agents aren't
in your purview, Detective.
맞습니다.
You got that right.
총구를 좀
낯춰 주시겠습니까?
Could you maybe lower your gun?
딕스 형사와
함께 있는 줄
알았습니다.
I thought Detective
Deeks was with you.
제가 실수를
한것 같네요.
Seems I was mistaken.
딕스 형사는 저와
함께하지 않습니다.
No, Detective Deeks
is not with me.
그한테 뭘
원하죠?
What do you want with him?
죄송하지만,
Well, I'm afraid I can't
진행 중인수사에 대해선
말씀드릴 수가 없습니다,
블라이 요원.
discuss ongoing investigations
with you, Agent Blye.
하지만 당신
파트너에 대해
But if you have something
you want to tell me
제게 하고싶은
얘기가 있다면
about your partner,
이리로 전화
주세요.
here's where you can reach me.
딕스는 정직한
경찰입니다.
Deeks is an upstanding
police officer.
LAPD중 최고죠.
The best LAPD has.
당신은 시간 낭비
하고있는 겁니다.
You're wasting your time.
그는 당신에게 아주
특별한 존재같군요.
He must be very special to you.
당신은
암껏두 찾지
못할겁니다.
You're not gonna find anything.
네, 아마도요.
Maybe not.
그렇다고
없다는 뜻은
아니죠.
Doesn't mean it isn't there.
강압적이었다는
얘기군요.
You're talking about coercion.
덫에 걸렸고.
Entrapment.
제 조카를 체포한 건
불법입니다.
My nephew's arrest was illegal.
그럼 이 공격들은
당신 조카의 복수를
하기 위한건가요?
And so, these attacks, this is
your way of... avenging him?
복수요?
Revenge?
아닙니다.
No.
제가 한 말을
듣기는 한겁니까?
Haven't you heard a word I said?
제가 취해온 행동들이
이해가 안가나요?
Haven't you understood
the action I've taken?
당신을 3명은
냉혹하게 죽였어.
You killed three people
in cold blood.
이해하기가
좀 힘들구만.
It's kind of hard to understand.
나비드를 데려간
첫 달 동안은
In the first months
after Naveed was taken,
저도 화가 났던걸
인정합니다.
I will admit I was angry.
복수의
이를 갈았죠.
I craved revenge.
하지만 곧 그게 얼마나
부질없는 생각인지
알게 됐습니다.
But then I saw how useless
those feelings were.
전 마음을 다스리는
방법을 배웠습니다.
I learned to control them,
더 고상한 목표를
이루기 위해서 말이죠.
to cast them aside
for a higher purpose.
알라군요.
Allah.
교육입니다.
캘런 요원.
Education, Agent Callen.
교육입니다.
Education.
저희를 가르치고
계시는 군요.
You're teaching us a lesson.
FBI의 자체
교육 방침을
따른겁니다.
By using the FBI's
own lesson plan.
가장 무시무시한
테러 계획은
Did you know that
the most terrifying plans
테러리스트에 의해
만들어진게 아니라는 걸
당신들, 아십니까?
for terrorist attacks
were not created by terrorists?
그것들은
여기서 개발됐죠.
They were developed here.
미국 안에서,
In the United States.
FBI에
의해.
By the FBI.
벌침 작전을
위해서 군요.
For sting operations.
사실 입니다.
It is true.
사실, 나비드에게
배정된 잠복요원이
그의 고등학교를
In fact, the undercover agent
assigned to Naveed gave him
날려 버리자는
아이디어를 줬습니다.
the idea to blow up
his own high school.
당신이 그 공격을
마무리 하려고
계획했나요?
And you plan to finish
that attack?
오, 아닙니다.
Oh, no.
그랬다면 그건
개인 원한이죠.
That would be too personal.
제가 분명
말씀드렸지만,
And as I've made clear,
이건 제
개인적인 게
아닙니다.
this is not about me.
당신들 방법이
잘못 됐다는 것을
보여주기 위한겁니다.
This is about showing you
the error of your ways.
오늘 5:37에
At 5:37 today,
당신들 정부에서
기획하고 개발한
one of those attacks--
conceived and developed
공격 중 하나가
드디어
by your own government--
will finally come
결실을
볼겁니다.
to fruition.
당신들이 그 모든
일을 했습니다.
You did all the work.
전 그냥 계획에
따랐을 뿐입니다.
I just followed your plan.
뭘 찾아냈나?
What have you found?
지난달 FBI
서버에 대한
Last month
there was a coordinated
합동 사이버 공격이
있었습니다.
cyber attack
on FBI servers.
온라인 상으로
수만개의 문서가
Tens of thousands
of documents
유출 되었습니다.
were downloaded
and leaked online.
벌침 작전의
기밀문서도
거기 포함됐죠.
Including classified details
of sting operations.
샤하가 그 문서들에
접근 했었겠군.
So, it's conceivable Shah has
access to this information.
저의 나나도
그렇습니다.
It's conceivable
my Nana does.
그녀는 정말
컴퓨터를 잘합니다.
Well, she's really good
at computers.
자네는 샤하가
문서 유출에
관여 했다고 보나?
You think it's possible Shah was
involved with the data breach?
가능성
있습니다.
It's possible.
하지만, 그 확율은
낮은 것 같습니다.
However, I don't believe
it's probable.
어나니머스(익명)로 부터
떨어져 나온
A group that splintered off
from Anonymous
한 그룹이 결국
책임을 떠 맡았습니다.
eventually
took responsibility.
사실은, 이런 류의
해킹은
The truth is,
these sorts of hacks
거의 매주 마다
발생하고 있습니다.
happen on an almost
weekly basis now.
하지만 이런 사실은
샤하가 어떻게
But it explains
how Shah would know
비밀 벌침작전에 대해
알 수 있었는지를
설명해 줍니다.
about the undercover
sting operation.
이 공격 중
일부는
These are some
그 문서에 자세히
나와 있습니다.
of the attacks detailed
in the reports.
관공서 건물,
교회 등...
Government buildings,
churches...
발전소, 교량,
철도 등등.
Power plants, bridges, railways.
마치 수퍼악당의
할일 목록 찾기
하는 것 같네요.
It's like finding
a supervillain's bucket list.
샤하의 최근
활동부터
조사해 줘.
Start tracking Shah's
recent activity.
그가 만일 뭔가
계획 중이라면
If he's planning
something,
그의 움직임이
그게 뭔지
알려 주겠지.
his movements may
show what it is.
알았습니다.
You got it.
컨웨이 요원이 그 누구보다
이번 공격에 대해
잘 알고 있을거야.
Agent Conway will know more
about these attacks than anyone.
난 FBI에
전념할게.
I'm gonna head over to the FBI.
그녀와 함께
목표를 좁혀 봐.
Work with her,
narrow the targets.
샤하를 계속
밀어부쳐 볼께.
I'll keep pushing Shah.
딕스가 그 조카로부터
뭔가 알아내길 바라자구.
Let's hope Deeks can get
something out of the nephew.
서둘자구.
The clock is ticking.
형사님이세요?
You're a detective?
그렇다네.
Yeah.
TV에서 보던
형사 같지 않네요.
You don't look
like they do on TV.
TV엔 어떻게
나오는데?
What's... what do they
look like on TV?
예를 들면,
양복입은
Like suits?
프로 같은?
You know, professional?
헤, 난 이미 예전에
양복 차려 입는다고
Yeah, well, I learned
a long time ago
프로가 되는 게
아니라는 걸
배웠다네.
that wearing a suit doesn't
make you professional.
또한, 자살폭탄
조끼를 입는다고
I also learned that wearing
다 테러리스가
되는게
a suicide vest
doesn't necessarily
아니라는 것도
배웠지.
make you a terrorist.
그래서 여기
오신건가요?
Is that why you're here?
제가 한 일
혹은
Because of what I did?
하려던 일
떄문에?
Or... tried to do?
사실, 나비드, 난
자네 삼촌이
Actually, Naveed,
I'm here to talk
한 일에 대해
얘기하러 온거네.
about something your uncle did.
전 지난 몇달간
삼촌과 얘기 해본
적이 없어요.
I haven't spoken
to my uncle in months.
절 여기 데려온
후가 아니라.
Not since they sent me here.
알아, 확인
해 봤어.
I know, I checked the log.
사실 방문객이
하나도 없었지.
You actually haven't had
any visitors.
날 뺴면 말이야.
Except for me.
삼촌은 저와
전화로도 얘기
안하려고 합니다.
He won't even talk
to me on the phone.
매번 그냥
끊습니다.
He hangs up every time.
그는 오늘 아침
FBI 요원 3명을
죽였네.
He killed three FBI agents
this morning.
그가 밴 안에
폭탄을 심었지.
He planted a bomb
inside of a van,
그리곤 그들을
날려 버렸다네.
and then he blew them up.
제 삼촌이요?
My uncle?
그가 그런게
확실한가요?
You're sure it was him?
그래, 그가
자백했어.
Yeah, he confessed.
그는 또한, 또 다른
공격이 계획됐고,
He also said that he has
another attack planned,
앞으로 두시간안에
시행 될거라고
얘기 했다네.
and that it's gonna be carried
out in the next two hours.
그게 내가
여기 온 이유야.
which is why I'm here.
그러니 자네가
뭔가 알고 있고
그걸 우리에게
So, if you can tell us anything,
if you know anything
얘기해 줄 수 있다면
도움이 될텐데...
that can help us...
지금 말이지.
now is the time.
저도 돕고 싶습니다.
I do want to help.
오케이.
Okay.
제 삼촌이
My uncle.
가능한 한 많은
I want to help him kill
연방 요원을
죽일 수 있도록
돕고 싶습니다.
as many federal agents
as possible.
저도 삼촌
바로 옆에서
I wish that I were standing
by his side,
이 악의 나라에 맞서
싸울 수 있었으면
좋겠습니다!
fighting this evil country.
이제야 삼촌이 왜
저를 안 보려 했는지
알겠습니다.
I understand now
why he wouldn't see me.
왜냐하면 그는 성전을
치루고 있었으니까요.
Because he was fighting
a holy war.
나도 이제
이해가 된다네.
Well, I understand now, too.
제 삼촌을 또 보시거든
"알라후 악바르"라고
전해 주십쇼.
Next time you see my uncle,
tell him "Allahu Akbar!"
"알라후 악바르"
Allahu Akbar!
켄지, 무슨 일이죠?
Hey, Kens, what's up?
넬, 난 지금
레익뷰 정비소에 있어.
Nell, I'm at Lakeview Auto.
그들은 화물트럭을 이용한
네바퀴 견인 서비스도
제공한다고 광고를 하는데
They advertise flatbed towing
as one of their services.
여긴 두바퀴 들고오는
견인 차량밖에 안 보여.
Problem is, I only see
a wheel lift truck.
네, 잠시만요.
Okay, let me see.
레익뷰 정비소에
견인용 화물트럭이
Yup, Lakeview Auto does show
one flatbed truck
한 대 등록
되어 있네요.
registered to them.
여긴 없어.
And it's not here.
공격에
사용된걸까?
It's being used in the attack?
만화경에 올리고
시 전체에 수배령을
내리겠습니다.
Putting it through Kaleidoscope
and sending out a citywide APB.
바로 돌아갈게.
I'm heading back.
여유 인력을
모두 보내세요.
All right, send
anyone we can spare.
한가지 더
있습니다.
Got another.
올림픽가에
유대교 회당이
하나 있습니다.
There's a synagogue on Olympic.
특별히 '에렙 욤 키퍼'
예배를 위한 곳이죠.
그런데...
It specifically targets an
Erev Yom Kippur service, but...
5개월 전까진
그랬죠.
It was five months ago.
지금은 금요일과 토요일에
일반 예배를 보고 있습니다.
Normal services are
on Friday and Saturday.
나중에 후회하느니
조심하는게 나은거죠.
Well, better safe than sorry.
그리고 전 나비드의 고등학교
건물을 소개시키기 위해
LAPD 경찰들을 파견했습니다.
And I've dispatched LAPD to
evacuate Naveed's high school.
잘하셨군요.
그런데 그게
목표가 아닙니다.
Good. It's not the target.
단지 테러범들이
아니라고 했다고 해서
Just because a terrorist
says it's not,
정말 아닌 건 아니죠,
샘 요원.
doesn't mean that it isn't,
Agent Hanna.
샤하가 그의 고상한 목적은
교육이라고 했습니다.
Look, Shah said that his
higher purpose was education.
그 말이면 제가
학교를 지켜야만하는
충분한 이유가 됩니다.
And that is enough for me
to keep the school in play.
샤하는 폭탄을
쓸 필요조차
없습니다.
Shah doesn't even
have to use a bomb.
수많은 가짜 테러범을
우리에게 던져 넣고
By throwing hundreds of
potential targets at us,
우리로 하여금
LA에 널린 건물들을
소개시키도록 하는거죠.
he's forcing us to evacuate
buildings all over L.A.
그는 그의 목적을
이루고 있는겁니다.
He's achieving
his goal-- panic,
공황과 공포...
미국산 테러입니다.
fear... American-made terror.
디음 공격까지
한시간도 채
안 남았습니다.
We got less than an hour
before the deadline.
일단 그의 장단을
잘 맟춰 줘야
할지 모릅니다.
We may well have
to play right into his hands.
- 샘
- 시간이 없네, G
Sam.
Running out of time, G.
그를 굴복시켜야 돼.
You need to break him.
샘, 자네도 들었잖아.
개인적인게 아니라고.
Sam, you heard him--
this isn't personal.
그는 공격 수단을
안 알려주고있어.
He's not giving us
any ammunition.
그 시계.
The watch.
5:37,
나비드 체포시간.
5:37-- Naveed's takedown time.
그게 우리가가진
전부야.
It's all we've got.
전화 다시할께.
I'll get back to you.
당신 조카,
나비드한테
Naveed, your nephew?
당신이 이
시계를 줬어.
You gave him this watch.
그 이유가
뭐라고 했지?
What-what was the reason again?
시간 잘 지키는 걸
배우라고 했다고?
You wanted to teach him
about, uh, being on time?
책임감을
가르치려 했다고?
To teach him about
responsibility?
하지만 당신은 여기서
당신 스스로 그걸
무시하고 있잖아.
But here you are,
shrugging off your own.
By blaming the FBI,
the-the U.S. government.
FBI와 미국 정부를
비난하며 말이야.
근데 말이지,
The thing is...
우린 당신 조카를
테러리스트로
we didn't turn your nephew
만들지 않았어.
into a terrorist.
당신이 한거지.
You did.
당신의 형,
그의 아내?
Your brother, his wife?
그들은
그들의 아들이
They died believing
that their son
돌봄과, 보호
그리고 좋은 삶을
was gonna be cared for,
제공 받을거라
믿으며 죽었어.
guided, provided
with a good life.
나비드는
Naveed was
당신의
책임이였고
your responsibility...
당신은
실패했지.
and you failed.
이제야 전부
말이 되네.
It all makes sense now.
그래서 조카가
체포된 후로 단 한번도
찾아가지 않았구만.
That's why you've never gone to
visit him since he was arrested.
그래서 전화 통화 조차
거의 안 했던거고.
It's why you can't bear to
speak with him on the phone.
그가 당신의 실패를
상기시키는거야.
He reminds you of your failure.
자기가 창조한 괴물을
마주할 수 없었던거지.
You can't stand to face
the monster you've created.
아니오!
No!
아님, 당신 스스로의
얼굴을 마주할 수
없었던건가?
Or maybe you can't
face yourself.
어쩌면 여태까지
내내 거짓말을
하고 있었겠군.
Maybe you've been lying
this entire time.
하지만
나한텐 안돼지.
But not just to me.
고상한 목적이라?
웃기는 소리 하고있네.
Higher purpose, my ass.
내내 개인적인
이유 말고는
암껏두 아니었다구.
It's never been anything
but personal with him.
그는 복수를 원하네
캘런 군.
He wants revenge,
Mr. Callen.
간단하면서
만족스러운
복수.
Simple, satisfying revenge.
우리가 허둥지둥
공격 계획을 찾아
헤메게 끔
Making us scramble to find
the right attack plan--
만드는
계략이군요.
that was all a ruse.
그 말은...
Meaning...
공격 목표는
오늘 아침 이래로
변함없이 FBI네.
the target remains the same
as this morning: the FBI.
나쁜 소식입니다.
켄지의 잃어버린
화물트럭을 찾았습니다.
Bad news. I just found
Kensi's missing flatbed truck.
That sounds like good news,
Ms. Jones.
내가 듣기엔
좋은 소식 같구만,
존스 양.
그런데 그게 지금 막
10번 고속도로에서
팜스 쪽으로 빠져
Yeah, but it just turned
off the 10 onto Palms Boulevard.
마르 비스타로
향하고 있습니다.
It's heading for Mar Vista.
FBI 특별팀 사무실이
있는 곳이군.
The FBI Task Force office.
Sam.
샘이 간 곳이지.
여러분, 이건
훈련이 아닙니다.
This is not a drill, people.
지금 모두 건물 뒷편으로
나가 주시기 바랍니다.
I need everyone out of
the back of the building now.
방패막이로 쓰려고
차들을 이동 중입니다.
They're moving vehicles
as a makeshift barrier,
하지만 충분하질
않습니다.
but it's not gonna be enough.
건물은
신경 안씁니다.
I don't care about the building.
사람들만 다
빠져 나가면 돼죠.
I just want to get
my people out.
라이언,
걍 두고 가.
Ryan, leave it.
해나 요원,
당신도 가세요.
가요.
That means you, too,
Agent Hanna. Go.
알았슴돠.
Okay.
바로 따라
나오셔야 합니다.
You better be right behind me.
그럴께요.
I will.
자, 전부 오세요.
Come on, everyone.
저위에 싣고 가는
저 차는 어디서 난거죠?
The car it's carrying--
where did it come from?
볼드윈 힐에 살고있는
히바 밬자리 소유입니다.
Belongs to Hiba Bakhzari,
resident of Baldwin Hills,
조나단과 오마르의
모친입니다.
and, uh, mother
of Jonathan and Omar.
FBI가 내내 그들의
온라인 활동을
감시해 왔는데,
The FBI has been monitoring
their online activity.
그들은
지난 한해
They've visited a number
급진적 웹사이트들을
수차례 방문했습니다.
of radical Web sites
over the last year.
샤하가 그렇게
동생들 다시
찾았겠군요.
- That must be how Shah found them.
- Brothers again.
18 및 17살 짜리.
18 and 17.
그들은 FBI로부터
불과 10분 거리에 있어요.
Hey, they're about
ten minutes away from the FBI.
저 차에 폭탄을
설치했다에
얼마 걸래?
How much you want to bet they
turned that car into a bomb?
샘에게 우리가
간다고 말해 줘.
Tell Sam we're
on our way.
잠깐,
같이 간다구요?
Wait. Together?
하지만
헤티가...
But Hetty said...
이게 당신
계획인가?
This is your plan?
애들을 강제로
조정하는게?
To coerce and
manipulate kids?
FBI가 사용하는 방법을
그들에게 고대로 쓰겠다고
말했잖습니까.
I told you I would use the FBI's
own methods against them.
애들이
죽는다구요!
They'll die.
제 뜻이
달성되는거죠.
And my point will be made.
뜻 같은소리
하지마쇼.
You don't have a point.
당신은 내게
거짓말을 해 왔어.
당신 자신에게도.
You've lied to me, and
you've lied to yourself.
단지 인정하기
싫은거지.
You just can't admit it.
괜찮아요,
우리 편입니다.
It's okay.
They're with me.
NCIS입니다.
NCIS.
에릭, 트럭이
얼마나 멀리있지?
Eric, how far away is the truck?
잉글우드에
접어들었습니다.
4분 거리입니다.
Turning onto Inglewood.
Four minutes out.
자넨 여기 남아서
I need you to stay here
FBI가 그 애들을 사살하지
못하도록 해 줘.
and make sure the FBI
doesn't take those boys out.
알았어.
On it.
- 계획이 뭐죠?
- 모두 살리는 거야.
What's the plan?
Keep everyone alive.
이게 당신 기회야,
샤하.
This is your chance, Shah.
당신이 책임을
질 수 있는
기회라구.
This is your chance to
take responsibility.
그 애들을
위해서.
For these boys.
그들에게 벌어진
일을 위해서.
For what happens to them.
이게 당신이 당신 적들보다
나아질 수 있는 기회라구.
This is your chance to be
better than your enemy.
이들을 봐.
Look at them!
당신은 복수가
아니라고 하지만
You say you're not
about revenge,
우릴 가르치고
있는 것도 아니야.
but you're also not about
teaching us a lesson,
그럼, 대체 뭘 위한거야?
so what are you about?
저기.
그들이다.
There.
That's them.
옆에 바짝 붙어 봐.
Get alongside them.
당신은 당신 조카가
더 많은 기회를
가져야 마땅하다고 믿지.
You believe that your nephew
deserved more of a chance.
이 모든 젊고
잘못 인도 된
You believe that
all of these young,
젊은이들이 그래야
마땅하다고 믿잖소.
misguided kids
deserve that.
나도 그렇게
믿습니다.
I do, too.
그들에게
전화를 하세요.
Call them.
공격을 멈추라고
말하세요.
Tell them to stop this.
그럴 수 없습니다.
I can't.
그들은 전화를
안 가지고 있습니다.
They don't
have a phone.
제가 가지고 있지
말라고 했습니다.
I told them not to take one.
죄송합니다.
I'm sorry.
정말 죄송합니다.
I am so sorry.
이제 모든게
알라신의 손에
달린 것 같군요.
Well, I guess this really is
in Allah's hands.
더 가까이.
Closer.
창문으로 나가.
그렇지.
Out the window-- good choice.
좋아,
조심해.
All right, watch it.
총 집어서 쏴,
그를 쏘라구.
Get the gun.
Shoot him. Shoot him!
헤이.
Hey.
들어 봐.
Listen.
총은 내려 놓을게.
I'm putting the gun down.
조나단이지?
Jonathan, right?
오마르?
Omar?
친구들,
난 샘이야.
Guys, my name is Sam.
우린 폭탄을
가지고 있어요.
We got a bomb.
터트릴 겁니다.
We'll blow it.
조나단,
자네한테
문제가 있네.
Jonathan, you got a problem.
자넨 임무를
끝낼 수 없어.
You're not gonna
complete your mission.
저 앞엔 FBI가 깔렸고
그들이 널 쏠거야.
There are agents up ahead--
they're gonna shoot you
그리고 네 동생도
일을 끝내기 전에.
and your brother
before you make it.
내가 명령하면
그들을 사살한다.
On my command,
you take them out.
그들이 십대
애들이라는 걸
당신도 아시죠?
You do realize they're
just teenagers, right?
차에 폭탄을
가득 싣고있는.
With a car full of explosives.
샘에게 자기 일을
할 수 있도록
시간을 좀 주시죠?
I'm just saying, give
Sam time to do his job.
딕스 형사,
만일 저 트럭이
입구에 들어서면
Detective Deeks, if that truck
reaches our driveway,
전 제가 해야할
일을 할겁니다.
I'm doing what needs to be done.
자네들을 이 일에
끌어들인 사람은
The man who put you up to this--
단지 개인적 복수를
하기 위해 그런거야.
this is for his own
personal vendetta.
이건 자네들 믿음과는
전혀 관계없는 일이야.
This has nothing to do
with your beliefs.
자네들은 그에게
이용당하고 있다구.
He's taken advantage of you.
자네 둘은 엄마가 있지?
You two have a mother, right?
자네들이 이걸 하면
어떻게 생각 하실까?
What will she think
if you do this?
자네들은 앞날이
구만리야.
You got your whole lives
ahead of you.
- 조준하도록.
- 안돼요. 아직 샘이
저기 있습니다.
On my mark.
No, Sam is still in the line of fire.
- 그를 끌어 내.
- 샘이 저기 있다구요.
Get him out of here.
Sam is in the line of fire!
안돼, 안돼.
No, no!
동생에게
기회를 줘.
Give your brother a chance.
조나단, 네
자신에게도
기회를 주리구.
Jonathan,
give yourself a chance.
이 일을
그만두게.
You don't have
to do this.
그들이
정지 중이야!
They're stopping!
기다려.
사격 중지.
Wait. Hold your fire.
잘했어,
조나단.
It's okay, Jonathan.
죄송합니다.
I'm sorry.
잘했어.
It's okay.
그들이 살았소.
They lived.
하지만 그들
인생은 끝났지.
But their lives
are over.
당신 조카처럼.
Just like your nephew's.
당신 책임이야.
That's on you.
데려가.
Take him.
내 요청을
묵살했더군.
You ignored my request.
그게, 우린
파트너고...
Well, we're partners, and...
파트너는 함께
일하는 거고, 해서...
partners work together, so...
내사과 소속
재클린 리베라
형사더군요.
Detective Jacqueline Rivera,
Internal Affairs.
왜 저희에게
얘길 안 해
주셨나요?
Why didn't you tell me?
내가 좀 더 알게되기 전까진
자넬 걱정하고 싶지 않았네
딕스 군.
I didn't want to worry you,
Mr. Deeks, until I knew more.
흐음.
Hmm.
그래 좀 더
알게 되셨나요?
So, do you know more now?
LAPD가
그들 스스로,
It would seem that the LAPD,
혹은 어떤
외압에 의해서
either on their own or...
수사를 하나
전개하기로
with some outside influence,
한 것 같다네.
바로
has decided to open
an investigation
자네에
대해서.
into you.
왜죠?
뭣땜에?
Why? What for?
지금으로서는 그들이
아주 바짝 숨기고
For now, they seem
to be playing their cards
카드놀이를
하고 있는것 같다네.
very close to the vest.
절대 실수도 안하고...
And make no mistake...
사냥을
하는 중이지.
...they're hunting.
그리고 그들은 자네에 대하여
가진 모든걸 사용할거야.
And they will use everything
they have against you.
저군요.
Me.
내가 자네 둘 다를
보호해 줄거야.
I will protect
you both
최선을 다해서.
the best I can,
하지만 만일 LAPD가
자네를 무너뜨리기 위해
but if there is
anything else
사용할 수 있는
또다른 뭔가가 있다면
that the LAPD can use
against you, Mr. Deeks,
지금 말하는게
좋을거야.
now is the time to speak up.
아무것도
없습니다.
There's nothing.
좋아.
All right.
둘 다
집으로 가게.
Go home, both of you.
밤 길
조심하고.
Watch the shadows.
이제
시작일 뿐이야.
This is just beginning.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Ah.
Oh, okay...